A Guide to the Trilateral Commission (North America) records FA420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings, 1972-2001; 1; 42.06 Cubic Feet 90 letter document boxes and 6 record storage boxes
  - Other Meetings, 1.3
    - Stephen Bosworth North American Event - Invitations, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 1058)
    - 25th Anniversary Evening and Publications - General, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 1059)
- Task Force Reports/Projects, 1973-2001; 2; 44.99 Cubic Feet 115 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  Apart from the gathering of the membership at meetings, the other major activity of the Trilateral Commission involves writing and distributing policy studies which are undertaken primarily through the creation, development and distribution of Task Force or Project reports, also known as the Triangle Papers.
  Task Force or Project Reports typically involved a team of authors from the three regions working together for a year or more to create a report. The report was often discussed, usually in draft form, at an annual meeting. Reports have usually been published and circulated widely once they are completed.
  There are several exceptions to this general rule: 1. Three reports had single authors: the 1985 Nishihara Report; the 1990 Israel-Pakistan FitzGerald paper; and the 1992 Gyohten paper. 2. Seven are signed individual essays, sometimes with a joint conclusion. 3. Several reports were completed with the help of outside/unaffiliated institutes such as the Atlantic Institute.
  In 1991-1992 three working groups were created – 1. Common Security Issues – which led to Report 43: Keeping the Peace in the Post-Cold War Era: Strengthening Multilateral Peacekeeping (1993). 2. Global Issues (Migration and Refugees) – which led to Report 44: International Migration Challenges in a New Era (1993). 3. Economic Interdependence – which served as the framework for Gyohten's Report 42: Regionalism in a Converging World (1992)
  Individual papers prepared in the context of these working groups were published in the 1992 Working Group Papers.
  The task force reports/projects permit intensive consideration of an issue, or a set of issues, and allow the participation of experts, including non-members, possibly from nontrilateral countries as authors, consultants or contributors. The reports often serve to provide context and perspective rather than recommending a set of specific policy directives.
  The topics are chosen by the Commission leadership (chairmen, deputy chairmen, and directors) with the advice of the Executive Committee and others.
  Topics include: 1. Economic Relations (monetary, fiscal, trade and investment policy); 2. Security (arms control, nuclear proliferation); 3. Energy issues (and the political implications of energy policies); 4. Relations among trilateral countries; 5. Relations with developing countries; 6. Relations with communist countries; 7. International institutions and political consultations.
  The task force reports/projects are reported to the Trilateral Commission, not of the Trilateral Commission. This distinction is an important one because attempting to reach a consensus among trilateral countries is often extremely difficult or impossible to achieve. The Commission in effect is not coming to a consensus on the issues being discussed; instead several appropriate individuals are chosen to investigate a topic and their findings are then reported to the Commission.
  A unique characteristic of the trilateral reporting process involves giving experts a forum within which to discuss issues, and to potentially seek multilateral long term solutions and common ground, without the pressures of national interests, which so often dominate bilateral negotiations between countries.
  This series is arranged numerically by Report Number (Task Force Reports 1-55). Accompanying files extend through Report 52 (1998).
  The Task Force files contained in the collection have accompanying "front matter" which chronicles the process by which each report was developed, often including various draft chapters and reports, correspondence between authors and/or authors meeting records and meetings with other consultants or experts. Accompanying files may also include publication arrangements, and documentation of press conferences and/or publicity.
  Box 209 contains two copies of most published reports. One copy is available of Report #37, #38, #39, #42 and #53. A final published version of Report #52 is not available in the archival collection. There is no individual copy of Report #9, but #9 is available in the combined volumes published by the NYU Press.
  Four draft reports were not completed for publication – Report #20: Major Payment Imbalances and International Financial Stability (1979); Labor Market Problems and Policies in Modern Trilateral Societies (no assigned #, 1980); Report #34: Science and Technology in Trilateral Relations: Competition and Cooperation (1987); and Report #47: Revitalizing Trilateral Democracies.
  Most reports were translated into Japanese. Many were translated into German. Some were translated into Spanish, French, Russian, and/or Italian. Translations are sporadically available within the body of the collection.
  Trilateral Commission - Task Force Reports (Triangle Papers)
  1. Towards a Renovated World Monetary System The Trilateral Commission (© 1973); Motoo Kaji, Richard N. Cooper and Claudio Segré. ISBN: 0-930503-61-9. Related Archival Material: Monetary Task Force (Box 95, 209, 308E). RAC Library: 339.5 KAJ.
  2. The Crisis of International Cooperation The Trilateral Commission (© 1974). François Duchêne, Kinhide Mushakoji and Henry Owen. ISBN: 0-930503-60-0. Related Archival Material: Political Task Force (Box 95, 209, 308E, 345).
  3. A Turning Point in North-South Economic Relations The Trilateral Commission (© 1974). Richard N. Gardner, Saburo Okita and B.J. Udink. ISBN: 0-930503-56-2. Related Archival Material: LDC Task Force (Box 96, 97, 209, 308E).
  4. Directions for World Trade in the Nineteen-Seventies The Trilateral Commission (© 1974). Guido Colonna Di Paliano, Philip H. Trezise and Nobuhiko Ushiba. ISBN: 0-930503-59-7. 36 pp. Related Archival Material: Trade Task Force (Box 97, 98, 209, 308E).
  5. Energy: The Imperative for a Trilateral Approach The Trilateral Commission (© 1974). John C. Campbell, Guy de Carmoy and Shinichi Kondo. ISBN: 0-930503-58-9. 36 pp. Related Archival Material: Energy Task Force (Box 98, 99, 209, 308F, 343).
  6. Energy: A Strategy for International Action The Trilateral Commission (© 1974). John C. Campbell, Guy de Carmoy and Shinichi Kondo. ISBN: 0-930503-57-0. 48 pp. Related Archival Material: Energy Task Force (Box 98, 99, 209, 308F, 343). RAC Library: 333.8 CAM.
  7. OPEC, the Trilateral World, and the Developing Countries: New Arrangements for Cooperation, 1976-1980 The Trilateral Commission (© 1975). Richard N. Gardner, Saburo Okita and B.J. Udink. ISBN: 0-930503-55-4. 32 pp. Related Archival Material: LDC Task Force (Box 96, 97, 209, 308E).
  8. The Crisis of Democracy Trilateral Commission © 1975, New York University Press. Michel Crozier, Samuel P. Huntington and Joji Watanuki. ISBN: 0-8147-1305-3. 220 pp. Related Archival Material: Democracies Task Force (Boxes 99, 100, 209, 356).
  9. A New Regime for the Oceans Trilateral Commission © 1976, New York University Press. Michael Hardy, Ann L. Hollick, Johan Jørgen Holst, Douglas M. Johnston and Shigeru Oda. ISBN: 0-930503-54-6. 54 pp. Related Archival Material: Oceans Task Force (Box 101, 102, 209, 308E).
  10. Seeking a New Accommodation in World Commodity Markets The Trilateral Commission (© 1976). Carl E. Beigie, Wolfgang Hager and Sueo Sekiguchi. ISBN: 0-930503-53-8. 40 pp. Related Archival Material: Access to Supplies Task Force (Box 102, 103, 209). RAC Library: 382 BEI.
  11. The Reform of International Institutions The Trilateral Commission (© 1976). C. Fred Bergsten, Georges Berthoin and Kinhide Mushakoji. 31 pp. Related Archival Material: Institutions Task Force (Box 104, 209, 356). RAC Library: 382 BER.
  12. The Problem of International Consultations The Trilateral Commission (© 1976). Egidio Ortona, J. Robert Schaetzel and Nobuhiko Ushiba. ISBN: 0-930503-51-1. 21 pp. Related Archival Material: Consultations Task Force (Box 104, 105, 209, 356).
  13. Collaboration with Communist Countries in Managing Global Problems: An Examination of the Options The Trilateral Commission (© 1977). Chihiro Hosoya, Henry Owen and Sir Andrew Shonfield. ISBN: 0-930503-47-3. 33 pp. Related Archival Material: Communist Involvement Task Force (Box 105, 106, 209).
  14. Towards a Renovated International System The Trilateral Commission (© 1977). Richard N. Cooper, Karl Kaiser and Masataka Kosaka. ISBN: 0-930503-46-5. 68 pp. Related Archival Material: Renovated International System Task Force (Box 107, 108, 209).
  15. An Overview of East-West Relations The Trilateral Commission (© 1978). Jeremy R. Azrael, Richard Löwenthal and Tohru Nakagawa. ISBN: 0-930503-42-2. 70 pp. Related Archival Material: East-West Task Force (Box 108, 109, 110, 209, 234, 308F). RAC Library: 337 TRI.
  16. Reducing Malnutrition in Developing Countries: Increasing Rice Production in South and Southeast Asia The Trilateral Commission (© 1978). Umberto Colombo, D. Gale Johnson and Toshio Shishido. ISBN: 0-930503-41-4. 55 pp. Related Archival Material: Food Task Force (Box 110, 111, 112, 113, 114, 115, 209, 308E). RAC Library: 337 TRI.
  17. Energy: Managing the Transition The Trilateral Commission (© 1978). John C. Sawhill, Keichi Oshima and Hanns W. Maull. ISBN: 0-930503-40-6. 92 pp. Related Archival Material: Energy Task Force (Box 115, 116, 117, 118, 119, 209). RAC Library: 337 TRI.
  18. Collective Bargaining and Employee Participation in Western Europe, North America and Japan The Trilateral Commission (© 1979). Benjamin C. Roberts, George C. Lodge and Hideaki Okamoto. ISBN: 0-930503-36-8. 90 pp. Related Archival Material: Labor-Management Task Force (Box 120, 121, 122, 123, 124, 209, 235). RAC Library: 337 TRI.
  19. Industrial Policy and the International Economy The Trilateral Commission (© 1979). John Pinder, Takashi Hosomi and William Diebold. ISBN: 0-930503-35-X. 82 pp. Related Archival Material: Industrial Policy Task Force (Box 124, 125, 126, 209, 347). RAC Library: 337 TRI & 338.91 PIN.
  20. Major Payments Imbalances and International Financial Stability The Trilateral Commission (© 1979, in draft form). Masao Fujioka, Alexandre Lamfalussy and Bruce K. MacLaury. Related Archival Material: Payments Imbalances Task Force (Box 127, 128, 129, 226).
  Unemployment and Smoothing Adaptation (No # assigned) The Trilateral Commission (© 1980, in draft form). Heinz Markmann, Richard Nelson, and Tadashi Hanami. Related Archival Material: Employment Task Force (Box 130, 131, 132).
  21. Trade in Manufactured Products with Developing Countries: Reinforcing North-South Partnership The Trilateral Commission (© 1981). Albert Fishlow, Jean Carrière and Sueo Sekiguchi. ISBN: 0-930503-29-5. 85 pp. Related Archival Material: North South Trade Task Force (Box 132, 133, 134, 135, 136, 137, 209, 327). RAC Library: 382 FIS.
  22. The Middle East and the Trilateral Countries The Trilateral Commission (© 1981). Garret FitzGerald, Hideo Kitahara, Arrigo Levi and Joseph Sisco. ISBN: 0-930503-28-7. 52 pp. Related Archival Material: Middle East Task Force (Box 138, 139, 140, 141, 142, 209). RAC Library: 327 MID.
  23. The Trilateral Countries in the International Economy of the 1980s The Trilateral Commission (© 1982). Miriam Camps, Ryokichi Hirono and Karsten Laursen. ISBN: 0-930503-24-4. 64 pp. Related Archival Material: New Vistas Task Force (Box 142, 143, 144, 145, 146, 209).
  24. East-West Trade at a Crossroads: Economic Relations with the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe Trilateral Commission © 1982, New York University Press. Robert V. Roosa, Michiya Matsukawa and Armin Gutowski. ISBN: 0-8147-7385-0. 119 pp. Related Archival Material: East-West Trade Task Force (Box 147, 148, 149, 150, 209, 226). RAC Library: 382 ROO.
  25. Sharing International Responsibilities Among the Trilateral Countries The Trilateral Commission (© 1982). Nobuhiko Ushiba, Graham Allison and Thierry de Montbrial. ISBN: 0-930503-20-1. 102 pp. Related Archival Material: Sharing Responsibilities Task Force (Box 150, 151, 152, 153, 209, 226). RAC Library: 337.1 USH.
  26. Trilateral Security: Defense and Arms Control Policies in the 1980s. The Trilateral Commission (© 1983). Gerard L. Smith, Paolo Vittorelli and Kiichi Saeki. ISBN: 0-930503-19-8. 106 pp. Related Archival Material: Trilateral Security Task Force (Box 153, 154, 155). RAC Library: 355 SMI.
  27. Facilitating Development in a Changing Third World: Trade, Finance, Aid The Trilateral Commission (© 1983). Takeshi Watanabe, Jacques Lesourne and Robert S. McNamara. ISBN: 0-930503-18-X. 126 pp. Related Archival Material: Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force (Box 155, 156, 157, 226). RAC Library: 338.91 WAT.
  28. Democracy Must Work: A Trilateral Agenda for the Decade Trilateral Commission © 1984, New York University Press. David Owen, Zbigniew Brzezinski and Saburo Okita. ISBN: 0-8147-6161-5. 88 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 158, 159, 209. RAC Library: 337 OWE.
  29. Agricultural Policy & Trade: Adjusting Domestic Programs in an International Framework Trilateral Commission © 1985, New York University Press. D. Gale Johnson, Kenzo Hemmi and Pierre Lardinois. ISBN: 0-8147-4168-1. 132 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 160, 161, 162, 163, 209. RAC Library: 338.1 JOH.
  30. East Asian Security & The Trilateral Countries Trilateral Commission © 1985, New York University Press. Masashi Nishihara. ISBN: 0-8147-5759-6. 111 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 163, 209. RAC Library: 355 SMI.
  31. Prospects for East-West Relations The Trilateral Commission (© 1986). William G. Hyland, Karl Kaiser and Hiroshi Kimura. ISBN: 0-930503-00-7. 52 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 163, 164, 209.
  32. Conditions for Partnership in International Economic Management The Trilateral Commission (© 1986). C. Fred Bergsten, Etienne Davignon and Isamu Miyazaki. ISBN: 0-930503-01-5. 56 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 165, 166, 209.
  33. Restoring Growth in the Debt-Laden Third World The Trilateral Commission (© 1987). Martin Feldstein, Hervé de Carmoy, Koei Narusawa and Paul R. Krugman. ISBN: 0-930503-02-3. 82 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 166, 167, 168, 169, 170, 209.
  34. Science and Technology in Trilateral Relations: Competition and Cooperation The Trilateral Commission (© 1988, in draft form). Takashi Mukaibo, Harold Brown and Luis Solana. Related Archival Material: Box 170, 171, 172, 173, 209.
  35. East Asia in Transition: Challenges for the Trilateral Countries The Trilateral Commission (© 1988). Richard C. Holbrooke, Roderick MacFarquhar and Kazuo Nukazawa. ISBN: 0-930503-04-X. 80 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 173, 173A, 209.
  36. East-West Relations The Trilateral Commission (© 1989). Valéry Giscard d'Estaing, Yasuhiro Nakasone and Henry Kissinger. ISBN: 0-930503-06-6. 23 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 174, 175, 176, 177, 209.
  37. International Financial Integration: The Policy Challenges The Trilateral Commission (© 1989). Shijuro Ogata, Richard N. Cooper and Horst Schulmann. ISBN: 0-930503-07-4. 28 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 177A, 178, 209.
  38. The Israeli-Palestinian Issue The Trilateral Commission (© 1990). Garret FitzGerald. ISBN: 0-930503-66-X. 42 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 179, 209.
  39. Latin America at a Crossroads: The Challenge to the Trilateral Countries The Trilateral Commission (© 1990). George W. Landau, Julio Feo and Akio Hosono. ISBN: 0-930503-62-7. 56 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 180, 181, 182, 209.
  40. Beyond Interdependence: The Meshing of the World's Economy and the Earth's Ecology Jim MacNeill © 1991, Oxford University Press. ISBN: 0-19-507126-3. 192 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 184, 185, 209.
  41. Global Cooperation After the Cold War: A Reassessment of Trilateralism The Trilateral Commission (© 1991). Joseph S. Nye, Jr., Kurt Biedenkopf and Motoo Shiina. ISBN: 0-930503-67-8. 64 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 186, 209.
  42. Regionalism in a Converging World The Trilateral Commission (© 1992). Toyoo Gyohten. ISBN: 0-930503-68-6. 16 pp. Related Archival Material: 209.
  43. Keeping the Peace in the Post-Cold War Era: Strengthening Multilateral Peacekeeping The Trilateral Commission (© 1993). John Roper, Masashi Nishihara, Olara Otunnu and Enid Schoettle. ISBN: 0-930503-70-8. 101 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 183, 186, 187, 188, 209.
  44. International Migration Challenges in a New Era The Trilateral Commission (© 1993). Doris Meissner, Robert D. Hormats, Antonio Garrigues Walker and Shijuro Ogata. ISBN: 0-930503-69-4. 116 pp. Related Archival Material: Migration and Refugees Working Group (Box 189, 190, 191, 192, 209).
  Structural Convergence Project, 1993-1994 (Aborted). Related Archival Material: Box 192.
  45. An Emerging China in a World of Interdependence The Trilateral Commission (© 1994). Yoichi Funabashi, Michel Oksenberg and Heinrich Weiss. ISBN: 0-930503-71-6. 84 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 193, 194, 195, 209.
  46. Engaging Russia The Trilateral Commission (© 1995). Robert D. Blackwill, Rodric Braithwaite and Akihiko Tanaka. ISBN: 930503-72-4. 139 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 195, 196, 197, 209.
  47. Revitalizing Trilateral Democracies The Trilateral Commission (© 1995, in draft form only). Robert D. Putnam, Jean-Claude Casanova and Seizaburo Sato. Related Archival Material: Box 198, 199, 209.
  48. Maintaining Energy Security in a Global Context The Trilateral Commission (© 1996). William F. Martin, Ryukichi Imai and Helga Steeg. ISBN: 0-930503-73-2. 117 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 200, 201, 202, 203, 209.
  49. Globalization and Trilateral Labor Markets: Evidence and Implications The Trilateral Commission (© 1996). Niels Thygesen, Yutaka Kosai and Robert Z. Lawrence. ISBN: 0-930503-74-0. 112 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 203, 204, 209.
  50. Managing the International System Over the Next Ten Years: Three Essays The Trilateral Commission (© 1997). Bill Emmott, Koji Watanabe and Paul Wolfowitz. ISBN: 0-930503-76-7. 62 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 204, 205, 209.
  51. Community-Building With Pacific Asia The Trilateral Commission (© 1997). Charles E. Morrison, Akira Kojima and Hanns W. Maull. ISBN: 0-930503-75-9. 123 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 205, 206, 207, 209.
  52. Advancing Common Purposes in the Broad Middle East The Trilateral Commission (1998). Robert H. Pelletreau, Reinhard Schlagintweit, Yoshiji Nogami and Dominique Moïsi. ISBN: 0-930503-77-5. 30 pp. Related Archival Material: 208.
  53. 21st Century Strategies of the Trilateral Countries: In Concert or Conflict? The Trilateral Commission (1999). Robert Zoellick, Peter D. Sutherland and Hisashi Owada. ISBN: 0-930503-78-3. 66 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 209.
  54. The New Central Asia: In Search of Stability The Trilateral Commission (2000). Alexander Rahr, Sherman Garnett and Koji Watanabe. ISBN: 0-930503-79-1. 79 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 209.
  55. East Asia and The International System The Trilateral Commission (2001). Coordinator: Charles E. Morrison. Other Authors: Wendy K. Dobson, Michel Oksenberg, Hisashi Owada, Hadi Soesastro. Study Group chair: Tadashi Yamamoto. ISBN: 0-930503-80-5. 88 pp. Related Archival Material: Box 209.
  56. Addressing The New International Terrorism: Prevention, Intervention and Multilateral Cooperation The Trilateral Commission (2003). Authors: Joseph S. Nye, Jr., Yukio Satoh and Paul Wilkinson. ISBN: 0-930503-81-6. 31pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  57. The "Democracy Deficit" in the Global Economy: Enhancing the Legitimacy and Accountability of Global Institutions The Trilateral Commission (2003). Authors: Joseph S. Nye, Jr. and others. ISBN: 0-930503-84-8. 96pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  58. The New Challenges to International, National and Human Security Policy The Trilateral Commission (2004). Anne-Marie Slaughter, Carl Bildt and Kazuo Ogura. ISBN: 0-930503-86-4. 66 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  59. Engaging with Russia: The Next Phase The Trilateral Commission (2006). Roderic Lyne, Strobe Talbott and Koji Watanabe. ISBN: 0-0-930503-87-2; 978-0-930503-87-1. 192 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  60. Nuclear Proliferation: Risk and Responsibility The Trilateral Commission (2006). Graham Allison, Hervé de Carmoy, Thérèse Delpech, and Chung Min Lee. Foreword by Henry Kissinger and Comment by Pierre Goldschmidt. ISBN-10: 0-930503-88-0; ISBN-13: 978-0-930503-88-8. 133 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  61. Energy Security and Climate Change The Trilateral Commission (2007). John Deutch, Anne Lauvergeon, and Widhyawan Prawiraatmadja. ISBN-13: 978-0-930503-90-1. 91 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  62. Engaging Iran and Building Peace in the Persian Gulf Region The Trilateral Commission (2008). Volker Perthes, Ray Takeyh and Hitoshi Tanaka. ISBN: 978-0-930503-91-8. 115 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  63. The Global Economic Crisis The Trilateral Commission (2011). E. Gerald Corrigan, Sir Callum McCarthy, Naoki Tanaka, Paul A. Volcker, and Bill Emmott. ISBN: 978-0-930503-93-2. 64 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  64. Nuclear Disarmament and Nonproliferation The Trilateral Commission (2011). Harold Brown, Graham Allison, Gilles Andréani, Kim Sung-han, Sergei Karaganov, Ariel E. Levite, Masashi Nishihara and Rajiv Sikri. ISBN: 978-0-930503-94-9. 120 pp. Related Archival Material: Not contained in collection.
  - Report #1: Towards a Renovated World Monetary System, 1973
    - Monetary Task Force - Drafts of 1973 Report (Box 95, Folder 1060)
    - Monetary Task Force - Drafts of 1973 Report (Box 95, Folder 1061)
    - Monetary Task Force - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1062)
    - Monetary Task Force - Substantive, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1063)
    - Monetary Task Force - Alaska Meeting, 1973 August 11-12 (Box 95, Folder 1064)
    - Monetary Task Force - Washington, D.C. Meeting, 1973 June 23-24 (Box 95, Folder 1065)
    - Monetary Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1066)
    - Monetary Task Force - Report Update, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 1067)
    - Monetary Task Force - Miscellaneous Integration Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 1068)
    - Monetary Task Force - Cooper Updates, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 1069)
    - Commissioners Comments on Cooper's Update, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 1070)
  - Report #2: The Crisis of International Cooperation, 1974
    - Political Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1071)
  - Report #3: A Turning Point in North-South Economic Relations (1974). Report #7: OPEC, the Trilateral World, and the Developing Countries: New Arrangements for Cooperation, 1976-1980 (1975), 1974, 1975
    - LDC Task Force - First Report - First Draft, 1974 April (Box 96, Folder 1072)
    - LDC Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 1073)
    - LDC Task Force - Correspondence, Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 96, Folder 1074)
    - LDC Task Force - First Report - Working Copies of Final Draft, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 1075)
    - LDC Task Force - First Report - Italian Version of Report and Lugano Review, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 1076)
    - LDC Task Force - Meetings, 1973 December 17-18 (Box 96, Folder 1077)
    - LDC Task Force - Meetings, Washington, DC, March 18-19, 1974 and New York, March 22, 1974, 1974 March 18 (Box 96, Folder 1078)
    - LDC Task Force - Meetings, New York, 1974 April 26-27 (Box 96, Folder 1079)